One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Thunder
الرعد
Have some more.
تفضل
Black Maria?
!بلاك ماريا
Hey, why aren't you working on your task?
لمَ لا تتكفلين بالمهمة؟
And what task would that be?
عن أي مهمة تتحدث؟
The search for my idiot son!
عملية البحث عن ابني الأحمق
Oh, what's the harm, Viceroy Kaido?
عجبًا، حالنا الآن طيب أيها القائد الأعلى كايدو
They can handle the search just fine without me.
أولئك التافهون يكفون لتولي هذه المهمة
I'd rather be here.
لهذا أنا هنا
Okay, fine! It's that time of year again to set aside rank and let loose!
لا أمانع، فاليوم هو الوحيد الذي نسترسل ونحتفل فيه
Right, Orochi?!
ألا تتفق معي يا أوروتشي في أن اليوم هو الأفضل؟
Right you are, Kaido!
فعلًا يا كايدو
The ghosts of the Kozuki Clan that haunted us for twenty years are finally gone!
بعد مُضي عشرين سنة، اختفت أشباح عشيرة الكوزكي اللعينة
It's a day for celebration!
هذه مدعاة للاحتفال
Kanjuro had them all fooled until the very last minute,
حان وقت إسدال الستار عن المسرحية الأخيرة
and now his career is complete after twenty long years!
فكنجورو الذي خدعهم طوال عشرين سنة على وشك الوصول
He'll soon arrive with the captains who sank the Red Scabbards into the sea!
ومعه ربابنة السفن الذين أغرقوا ساموراي الأغماد في أعماق البحر
He's an impressive one!
إن هذا لمثيرٌ للإعجاب
I could have easily killed him back then without realizing it.
كدت أقتله بالخطأ حينها
It's too bad though... Even after earning all that trust,
،ولكن كون أودين لم يفتح قلبه له رغم اكتسابه ثقته الشديدة
It's likely those samurai retainers have not heard anything about it either.
يعني أن جماعة الساموراي لم يخبرهم عنه كذلك
Are you talking about...?
أتعني ذلك الأمر؟
Yeah...
أجل
The key to the location of Laugh Tale, the last island that Roger reached.
دليلُ موقع الجزيرة الأخيرة لافتيل التي وصلها روجر
Who are you?!
من أنت؟
Pardon me!
المعذرة
I have business with Lord Orochi!
أريد مقابلة أوروتشي-ساما
Oh! There you are, Kanjuro!
!وصلت يا كنجورو
I've never seen him before.
لم أقابله قبلًا
You here for a fight?!
أتريد القتال أيها اللعين؟
Calm down, you idiots!
،اهدؤوا يا رجال
He's Orochi's man!
إنه تابع لأوروتشي
It has been too long, Lord Orochi!
أطلتُ المغيب عليك يا أوروتشي-ساما
The mansion is so massive that I got a little lost backstage.
القصر فسيح فضللت طريقي قليلًا
Kurozumi Kanjuro Shogun Orochi's Informant
كوروزومي كنجورو جاسوس الشوغن أوروتشي
I had to cut down all those men who mistakenly attacked me as their enemy.
ظن بعض أتباعك أنني عدو فاضطررت للإطاحة بهم
I apologize for that.
أعتذر بشأن هذا
Well, that's alright!
عمَ تتحدث؟ لا بأس في هذا
Oh! I see you've got something there...
ما هذا الذي تحمله في يسراك؟
It is Kozuki Momonosuke, per your request.
أحضرتُ كوزكي مومونوسكي كما طلبت مني
He is Oden's son.
إنه ابن أودين
He cut his ropes and attempted to escape on the way here, so I had to knock him out.
حلّ وثاقه وحاول الهرب ونحن قادمون فأفقدته وعيه
Do not fret. He is alive.
لا عليك... لا يزال حيًّا
So this is how you treat your former Kozuki lord's heir...
أمن المروءة أن تفعل هذا بوريث الكوزكي والذين كانوا أسيادك؟
How cold and heartless of you!
أنت رجلٌ عديم المشاعر وبلا قلب
Now that my act is over, he's just another whelp to me.
فرغت من تأدية دوري فباتَ مجرّدَ غريب
What a surprise!
فوجئت من ذلك، فأنا أتذكرك حقًّا
You're one of the Nine Red Scabbards that I fought against twenty years ago.
كنت أحد الأغماد التسعة الذين واجهتهم قبل عشرين سنة
And you... I definitely remember you.
كما أنني أتذكرك أنت أيضًا
Your father was brave, but you're nothing but a disappointment.
خاب ظني حين علمتُ أنك ابن الباسل أودين قبل عشرين سنة، وأراك لم تتغير حتى الآن
Indeed. He's nothing more than a miserable brat...
أجل، فهو مجرد صعلوك
who happened to inherit a great name.
...مُنيَ بنسبٍ مهيب فحسب
You poor thing.
...قد أفطرَ فؤادي
He's bleeding... How could you strike a little boy so hard?
كيف تسوِّل لك نفسك أن تلكم فتىً صغيرًا حتى تُدميه؟
It's time to drink! Let's make a toast!
لنشرب النخب حتى الثمالة
You've done well playing the part of spy for so long!
فقد نلت استحقاق الثناء عن خدمتك جاسوسًا جلّ معيشتك
Bravo!
أحسنت عملًا
No, Shogun Orochi!
!لا يا أوروتشي-ساما
I failed to intercept the Red Scabbards' plan...
...خطة الأغماد سارية كما هي
because the Straw Hats and their allies ambushed us!
فبسبب تدخل طاقم قبعة القش وبقية القراصنة فشلتُ في إحباطها...
What?! Failed?!
!فشلت؟
The rebel forces, 5,400 strong, are advancing toward Onigashima as we speak!
قوات المتمردين البالغة 4500 في طريقها إلى أونيغاشيما الآن
Unacceptable!
أتعبث معي؟
You failed to intercept their plan?!
!فشلتَ في إحباط خطتهم؟
I am deeply sorry!
!أستجدي العفو منك
You're the one who told me that they'd rendezvous at Tokage Port!
أنت من أبلغني عن نقطة الالتقاء التي تغيرت إلى ميناء توكاغي
Why didn't you exterminate them?!
فلِمَ لم تبطش بهم؟
K-Kin'emon outsmarted me!
فاقني كينيمون حنكةً
I have known him for a long time,
،عرفته لوقتٍ طويل
but I underestimated his tactical genius!
وما كان ظني به أن يكون فطنًا هكذا
Stop with the excuses!
!لا تعتذر
Answer me, Kanjuro!
،أخبرني يا كنجورو
Will the samurai fleet make it to Onigashima?!
!أسيبلغ أسطول الساموراي أونيغاشيما؟
It seems like we're still safe here, Shogun Orochi.
يظل هذا المكان في مأمن منهم يا أوروتشي-ساما
Fukurokuju!
!فوكوروكوجو
There are no suspicious ships at the port.
لم تصل سفن مثيرة للريبة إلى الميناء
However, three of our warships have yet to return.
ولكن ثلاثًا من سفننا الحربية لم تعد
In fact, we have confirmation of four pirates out on the Performance Floor.
بالأحرى، رُصد أربعة قراصنة في طابق العرض المباشر
Straw Hat Luffy.
قبعة القش لوفي
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
صائد القراصنة زورو
Eustass "Captain" Kid.
يوستاس كابتن كيد
Soldier of Slaughter Killer.
آلة القتل كيلر
It's very likely that the rest of their crews are also on the island.
وأرى احتماليةً لتسلل أفراد طاقميهما إلى الجزيرة أيضًا
If you knew that, why didn't you report it before?!
!لمَ لمْ تبلغني بهذا فور ما وصلكَ التقرير؟
Sir Queen was handling it,
،يتعامل كوين-دونو معهم
so I thought it'd be better not to spoil the banquet.
لذا فضلت ألَّا أُعكّر صفو المأدبة
Whether they're here or not, the fact remains that all of our forces are here on Onigashima.
وفي حال كانوا داخل أونيغاشيما؛ فكل قواتنا حاضرةٌ هنا
Whatever happens, this is the safest place in the country!
مهما حدث، فهذا المكان يظل أكثر المناطق أمانًا في البلاد
You said it!
أصبت
Drink up, Orochi!
اشرب يا أوروتشي
Here, let me pour you a cup.
تفضل، سأصب لك كأسًا
No... I don't want reassurances!
كلا، لا أحتاج إلى مواساة
I want a report that the damn samurai have been slain!
أُفضّل وصول نبأ مصرع أولئك الساموراي
Luffy made it inside...
...وصل لوفي لهذه الجزيرة إذًا
Keep yourself alive!
جِد وسيلة للنجاة
I'll rescue you for sure!
سنأتي لإنقاذك
I must escape!
عليّ الفرار بأي وسيلة
Black Maria!
بلاك ماريا
Give him to me!
اعطيني إياه
That's right! We mustn't forget! He's the leader of the enemy force!
هذا صحيح، علينا ألَّا ننسى أنه قائد الأعداء
Set the execution stage!
جهزوا منصة الإعدام
Once the renowned Kozuki family dies out, any sparks of loyalty left will fade away completely.
إن أسدلنا الستار عن نسل عشيرة الكوزكي فإن ولاءهم المبعثر سينهار هو الآخر
And it'll finally be over!
وسننتهي من كل هذا
Luffy...!
...لوفي
Everyone...!
...الجميع
Father...!
!أبتاه
Is that you, Cat?! You're late!
!القط؟ تأخرت
You only just arrived?!
أوصلت توًّا؟
Yeah! Sail: "Cat"
أجل
We just climbed up the falls!
كان علينا تسلق الشلال
Don't you know what day and time it is?!
ألا تعرف ما يمثله اليوم؟
It's the night of the Fire Festival, so we're just in time for the great battle, aren't we?
إنه يوم تنفيذ خطة ليلة مهرجان النار، لذا فأمورنا مستتبة
You-gara shouldn't say that until you get here.
أمورنا ليست مستتبة بعد
We're already on our way to the northwestern end of Onigashima.
نحن في طريقنا حاليًا إلى رأس أونيغاشيما الشمالي الغربي
Got it! See you later then!
فهمت، أراك لاحقًا إذًا
No, wait!
لا، مهلًا
Wait, hey!
!مهلًا
Cat!
!أيها القط
That impatience of his remains unchanged.
إنه عجول كعادته
I just hope they make it in time for our raid.
آمل أن يلحقنا في الوقت المناسب
I have not seen Kitty since we got separated...
لم ألتقيه منذ اليوم الذي افترقنا فيه
I bet he's as big as Doggy now, too.
لا شك أنه أصبح بضخامة الكلب-تشان
That damn cat... He'd better get here as fast as he can!
القط الوغد، عليه أن يتحرك بسرعة
We'll reach the rear door soon!
فسنصل إلى المدخل الخلفي قريبًا
Because of the whirlpools, normal ships can only approach the island from the front.
تيارات المحيط تجعل السفن العادية تقترب من الأمام فحسب
I hope Kin'emon and Denjiro were able to reach the rear door safely.
يُفترض أن كينيمون ودنجيرو وصلا للمدخل الخلفي سلفًا
Yes! I want all of us to fulfill Lord Oden's wish together!
أجل، فإرادة أودين-ساما تقع على عاتقنا جميعًا
Lord Momonosuke...
...مومونوسكي-ساما
Please be safe!
أتمنى سلامتك
Are they all okay?
هل جميعهم بخير؟
Yeah, of course they are!
هذا أكيد
He said everyone made it to the island already, so I guess the raid is underway!
ذُكر أن الجميع وصلوا إلى الجزيرة، لذا ظني أن الغارة بدأت
That lonely island is now called Onigashima, huh?
اسم «أونيغاشيما» هو ما اختاروه لتلك الجزيرة المنعزلة إذًا؟
Who would've thought that we'd arrive at the same time, even though you left before me?
سبقتني بالرحيل ومع ذلك وصلنا في الوقت ذاته
Turns out I didn't need to entrust you with my message to Straw Hat Luffy!
لا حاجة لتوصيل تلك الرسالة إلى قبعة القش لوفي بعد الآن-يوي
You're right!
،فعلًا
I'll throw this note out!
سأرمي الملحوظة
Anyway, I can't believe you came, Marco.
ما زلتُ متعجبًا من مجيئك يا ماركو
Well, I always did like Oden.
هذا لأنني طالما أعجبتُ بأودين
But I can't believe how much his country has changed...
ولكنني لا أُصدّق التغيّر الجذري الذي حل بموطن أودين
News about this place never crosses the sea.
لا تتناقل أخبار بلاد وانو عبر المحيط
I didn't know the once prosperous Wano had been reduced to such a state...
فلم يكن لي علمٌ أن بلاد وانو المزدهرة سابقًا أضحت على هذه الحالة
It's all because of Kaido.
كل هذا بسبب كايدو
If you've made up your mind, let's hurry on to Onigashima!
أرى العزم فيكما، فلنسرع إلى أونيغاشيما
We must catch up to everyone!
علينا أن نلحق بالجميع مهما كلّفنا الأمر
But what can we do?
رغم ذلك، ماذا علينا أن نفعل؟
The raid has already begun.
فغارتهم بدأت سلفًا
How will we slip past the enemy lines to join them?
كيف لنا أن ننضم إلى صفوفهم والأعداء من حولهم؟
Leave it to me!
اتركني لأتدبر الأمر، فقد خطرت لي فكرة
As planned, Denjiro is leading the southern forces to the castle's rear door.
يقود دنجيرو القوات الجنوبية نحو المدخل الخلفي للقلعة كما خُطِّط
There seems to be a gate here!
بوابةٌ في مكانٍ كهذا؟
Hide!
اختبئوا
Is he a top officer?
أهو من القادة؟ هذه مشكلة عويصة
Listen! Find him as quickly as possible!
اعثروا عليه سريعًا كما أمرتكم
– Yes, sir!
عُلم
On the contrary, it seems we have lucked out.
لا، ليست مشكلة
I know him.
أنا أعرفه
I will talk to him.
سأذهب إليه
Who goes there?!
من هناك؟
Wait, it's me!
على مهلك، إنه أنا
Aren't you...?
...أنت
It's been a while...
...طالت بيننا المهاجر
Sasaki Soaring Six Beast Pirates
ساساكي أحد التوبي روبو من قراصنة الوحوش
Sasaki!
!يا ساساكي
Kyoshiro!
!كيوشيرو
I heard you weren't coming this year!
بلغني أنك لن تأتي هذه السنة
Yeah, I ask that you keep this a secret.
أجل، حافظ على سرّي فضلًا
You're here incognito? What happened to that pompadour you were so proud of?
هل أنت متخفٍ؟ ماذا حلَّ بتسريحة شعرك البومبادور؟
It's unusual to see you away from the banquet.
من غير المألوف أن تغادر المأدبة
Yeah. Kaido's kid went missing.
أجل، إنَّ ابن كايدو-ساما مختفٍ
But hey, want a drink?
الأهم، أتودّ احتساء الشراب؟
You bet I do!
!طبعًا
Guys! Head back to the Skull Dome!
يا رفاق، عودوا إلى قبة الجمجمة
I'll join you later.
سألحق بكم لاحقًا
A gate that was missing from the blueprints. And one of the Soaring Six, Sasaki.
البوابة التي لم تكن في المخططات وفرد التوبي روبو ساساكي
Such obstacles would have been difficult for Kyoshiro to overcome
رغم ذلك، بالنسبة لكيوشيرو الذي اكتسب ثقة العدو لوقتٍ طويل
if he wasn't so trusted by the enemy.
كانتا عقبتان يسهل تذليلهما
Seastone?!
!حجر بحري؟
Hey, what's the big idea, Kyoshiro?!
ما الذي يجري يا كيوشيرو؟
Restrain him!
شُدُّوا وثاقه
– Yes, sir!
عُلم
What's going on?! Hey!
!ماذا تفعل؟
Gag him as well!
أطبقوا فمه أيضًا
– Yes, sir!
عُلم
Answer me, Kyoshiro!
أجبني يا كيوشيرو
Hey, Sasaki...
...يا ساساكي
How much do you know of Wano's history?
أتفقه في تاريخ بلاد وانو؟
Is that...?!
!هذا
After restraining one of the formidable Soaring Six,
بعدما أزاحوا أحد التوبي روبو صعبو المراس
Denjiro split his group into two, just as the eastern forces had.
قسَّم دنجيرو قواته إلى فرقتين كالقوات الشرقية
Get to the dome from here!
ادخلوا إلى القبة من هنا
Good luck!
!حظًّا سعيدًا
Dome Infiltration Team
فرقة التسلل إلى القبة
Thus, the southern forces are steadily closing in on Kaido!
وهكذا بدأت القوات الجنوبيَّة تضيق الخناق حول كايدو
Raid Team
قوات الهجوم
Eastern Forces Kin'emon's Group
القوات الشرقية فرقة كينيمون
Fire!
!أطلق
I won't let you get away!
لن تفلت مني
I knew it wouldn't work!
!إن هذا لمحالٌ كما ظننت
Of course it didn't!
!هذا جلي
They're gone!
رحلوا
Chobro!
...تشونيكي
That's one fierce mature woman...
...يا لشدّة نضجها وبأسها
Even though they were frightened, they still led her in the opposite direction...
رغم ذعرهم الشديد، إلا أنهم هربوا في الاتجاه المعاكس
We are in your debt, Commander Chopper, Driver Usopp...
أُشيد بكما أيها النقيب تشوبر وأيها السائق أوسوب
Let us carry on!
لنواصل التقدم
– Yeah!
أجل
Everyone! Do not let their sacrifice go to waste!
لا تدعوا تضحيتهما تضيع هباءً
Hey, shouldn't we do something?!
!اسمعا، ألا يجدر بنا التصرف؟
I think that monstrous mature woman is too much for those two boys to handle!
لن يقدر ذينك الفتيان على احتمال تلك المرأة الناضجة الشديدة
She's right!
هذا صحيح، فهي بيغ مام
I know!
كما أختبركما، لن نقدر على فعل شيء
Let's just be happy they lured her away!
لنكن ممتنين لهما لاستدراجها بعيدًا
In any case, why's it so hot in here?
الأهم من ذلك، أليسَ المكان حارًا هُنا؟
Nami! Look up!
انتبهي خلفكِ يا نامي
We're in trouble!
نحن في ورطة
I found you!
عثرت عليكِ
It's the woman who kidnapped Zeus, Mama!
!إنها مُختطفة زيوس يا ماما
Fight, Pay-Pay! Fight, Pay-Pay!
قاتل يا باي-تان، قاتل يا باي-تان
Hey! Go look somewhere else, you bonehead!
لمَ لا تبحثي في مكانٍ آخر؟
Excuse me, Pay-Pay?!
...لحظة يا باي-تان، أنت
But...
...ولكن
I can't run anymore...
لا أقوى على المواصلة
Pay-Pay! I'm ever so weary!
يا باي-تان، أنا مُرهقة-أرينسو
Woe is me!
!وا أسفاه على حالي
Don't cry about it to me!
لا تعيقيني، إن كنتِ مُرهقة فابقي مكانك
You're supposed to offer...
...لمَ لا تقول
Oh, no!
!مصيبة
...to carry me on your back!
«دعيني أحملكِ على ظهري»
Ulti and Page One Soaring Six Beast Pirates
أولتي وبيج ون التوبي روبو قراصنة الوحوش
Hey, get off of me! Hey!
لا تعيقيني
Wait! Let go of me! Big Sis!
على رسلكِ، أفلتيني يا أختي
You little...
...أيها
Hey! Stop it! I mean it!
بجديَّة، دعيني
Pay-Pay?!
!باي-تان
Pay-Pay! Pay-Pay! Pay-Pay!
!باي-تان، باي-تان، باي-تان
Stay with me, stay with me, stay with me!
تماسك، تماسك، تماسك من أجلي
Oh no, my Pay-Pay!
آهٍ يا باي-تان
What's that?
ما هذا؟
Pay-Pay!
باي-تان
Pay-Pay sacrificed himself to save me!
ضحى باي-تان بنفسه من أجل حمايتي
Who the hell are you?!
من أنت أيها اللعين؟
There it is... Onigashima.
أتلك... أونيغاشيما؟
King...
...كينغ
Marco...
...وماركو
Straw Hat...
...وقبعة القش
They'd better prepare themselves for a licking...
يجدر بهم الحذر-بيرورين
And no, I don't approve of Mama's alliance!
فأنا لا أعترف بهذا التحالف
The Big Mom Pirates will have the last lick!
ومن يضحك أخيرًا سيكون نحن، قراصنة بيغ مام
What now, Usopp?!
ماذا علينا أن نفعل يا أوسوب؟
Big Mom turned back to go after Nami and the others!
بيغ مام تطارد نامي والبقية
I guess she's trying to take back Zeus.
أظنُّها تريد استعادة زيوس
I'm worried about them...
...أنا قلق بشأن نامي والبقية
The transformation switch seems to have activated when she punched us.
يبدو أن تلك الضربة نجم عنها تفعيل مفتاح التحول
Well, I'm sure they'll be fine... Sanji's with them, too.
لا تقلق حيالهم، كما أن سانجي معهم
Sanji, huh?
أتقول سانجي؟
I hope he remembers to rescue Momonosuke instead of chasing women in the pleasure hall.
أتمنى ألا ينسى أهميَّة إنقاذ مومونوسكي بينما يطارد النساء في منطقة الملذات
I wouldn't rule that out...
هنالك احتمالية فعلًا
But let's trust Sanji!
لا، يجدر بنا أن نثق بسانجي
Yeah!
معك حق
Kin'emon's team was able to advance, so we're doing well!
تمكنت جماعة كينيمون من المضي قُدُمًا فنحن على المسار الصحيح
We showed them what the Brachio-Tank is capable of!
وكما أننا قد استعرضنا قدرات دبابة براكيو
Yeah! We're Commander Chopper and gunner Usopp driving the Brachio-Tank 5!
أجل، بفضل النقيب تشوبر والسائق القنَّاص أوسوب ودبابة براكيو 5
Nothing stands in our way!
لا يعترض شيء طريقنا
Inside the Pleasure Hall
داخل منطقة الملذات
Come along...
هيا بنا
An old umbrella.
مظلة قديمة
Old clogs and old sandals.
قبقاب وصندل قديمان
A dirt wall!
شمعة وقرميد
A lantern, too!
وفانوس أيضًا
I give you life!
أمنحكم الحياة
So follow me.
فاتبعوني
Mama, this way!
هنا، هنا يا ماما
Hey! Stop calling for Big Mom, sun!
ويحك، لا تستدعي بيغ مام إلى هنا يا شمس
What should I do, Nami?!
ما العمل يا نامي؟
If she catches me, I'm a goner!
ستقتلني ماما إن أمسكت بي
Is that overripe mature woman really that dangerous?
أتلك المرأة الناضجة الشديدة بتلك الخطورة حقًّا؟
She's on a whole different level!
أعجز عن وصف خطورتها
Hey, didn't we see Sanji a little while ago?
ألم نرَ سانجي-كن توًّا؟
Yeah!
بلى
Sorry for making you worry...
،أعتذر عن بث القلق في قلبكِ
I'm not giving up on finding those women!
لن أستسلم حتى أعثر على بغايا
What did he even come here for?!
فيمَ يفكر ذلك الأبله؟
In any case, we need to outrun her and look for Lord Momonosuke!
فلنهرب الآن ونعثر على مومونوسكي-ساما
Okay!
أجل
Mama! This way!
من هنا يا ماما
There's no need to rush.
لا تتعجل، فأمامنا طابق العرض المباشر
There's nowhere to run.
لا مهرب لكم
So many of these guys have powers…
يأتينا مستخدمو قدرات كثُر مرارًا
Call us Gifters.
نادنا بالغيفترز
We, too, once aimed to be King of the Pirates.
قد سعينا نحن أيضًا لنيل لقب ملك القراصنة في الماضي
If you bow down to Lord Kaido, things will be easier for you.
إن أطعت كايدو-ساما؛ فسيطيب لك العيش
There are almost 500 of us.
نبلغ قرابة الخمسمئة فرد
Don't make this hard on yourself.
ارضخ فحسب
It's not too late to start over.
لا تزال الفرصة سانحة للاستسلام
Kid! I told you it's too reckless to break through head-on!
كما توقعت، من التهوّرٌ أن نخترق صفوفهم يا كيد
We got separated from Heat and the others...
...فقدنا أثر فرقة هيت أثناء القتال
They were fighting right alongside us,
...ولكن طالما لم يُكشف تنكرهم
Wire Kid Pirates Heat
واير من قراصنة كيد هيت
but they'll be okay on their own.
سيكون كل شيء على ما يرام...
If we kill you guys, I bet we'll get promoted!
قتلكما سيتيح لنا فرصة تحسين مكانتنا
Please stop!
تمهل رجاءً
Lord Kaido is looking for you!
يبحث كايدو-ساما عنك
Stop bothering me!
لا تزعجوني، دعوني وشأني
– Young Master! Please stop!
توقف فضلًا أيها السيّد اليافع
Let down your guard and you die!
إرخاء دفاعكم يعني هلاككم
Pay-Pay!
!باي-تان
Pay-Pay! Are you okay?!
هل أنت بخير يا باي-تان؟
Don't leave me! I'd be ever so distraught!
تماسك من أجلي-أرينسو
Hey, you!
يا هذا
How could you...
...كيف تجرأت
How could you do this to Pay-Pay?!
كيف تجرأت على فعل ذلك بباي-تان؟
Don't you dare bully my Pay-Pay!
!لا تتنمر على باي-تان
You're the one who used him to ski down the stairs.
أنتِ من امتطى ظهره انزلاقًا على تلك السلالم
What's your name?!
من أنت؟
Who do you work for and which unit do you belong to?!
أخبرني عمّن تعمل تحت إمرته، ولأي مجموعة تنتمي
No, Big Sis...
أنتِ مُخطئة يا أختاه
He's an intruder.
إنه دخيل
What?!
ماذا قلت؟
I'm Luffy.
...أنا لوفي
The man who'll become the King of the Pirates!
الرجل الذي سيصير ملك القراصنة
Do you have any idea whose castle you're standing in?
هل تعرف قلعة من هذه؟
The one who will become King of the Pirates is obviously Lord Kaido!
من سيصير ملك القراصنة هو كايدو-ساما لا غيره
You freaking dumbass!
!يا بسيط التفكير الأحمق
I'll cave your damn skull in!
سأهشم جمجمتك
A headbutt?!
نطحة إذًا؟
Ulti-Mortar!
مدفع جمجمة أولتي
Hey, Big Sis!
يا أختاه
I know...
أعرف
Pay-Pay too?
هيا يا باي-تان
Yeah!
حسنًا
Excuse me, but...
...أعتذر عن المقاطعة
why did you two transform?!
لمَ تحول كلاكما؟...
Ulti Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Pachycephalosaurus
أولتي فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق باكيسيفالوصور
Master Ulti!
يا أولتي-ساما
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Master Page One!
ويا بيج ون-ساما
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Page One Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit Spinosaurus
بيج ون فاكهة تنين من النوع العتيق سبينوصورس
Master Ulti?
يا أولتي-ساما
Um...
...عذرًا
Quiet down, you.
يا لشدّة صخبك
We did it because...
...إن هذا
this guy is the real deal!
!الخطر بعينه وأنا بنفسي أعدّه خصمًا قويًا...
No, no, there's no way!
هيهات هيهات فرأسه شُجّ وقُتل إثر ذلك
Then how do you explain that haki?!
لمن يعود الهاكي الذي أستشعره إذًا؟
That hurt!
!لقد آلمتني
These guys are amazing...
ظهر أقوياء عدّة أمامي
I was wrong...
كنتُ مخطئًا في الاستخفاف بهم قليلًا
This castle belongs to an Emperor!
هذه قلعة إمبراطور
Listen up, ya jerks!
أيها الأوغاد
Performance Floor Skull Dome
طابق العرض المباشر قبة الجمجمة
Shogun Orochi presents an impromptu special event starting now!
الشوغن أوروتشي يقدم لكم حدثًا خاصًا مرتجلًا وسيبدأ الآن
Everyone!
...أيها الحضور، إن الصعلوك المترهل أمامكم
Lo and behold...
-وعلى نحو مفاجئ-
the son of Kozuki Oden, thought to have died twenty years ago!
ابن كوزكي أودين المُفترض هلاكه قبل عشرين سنة...
Gum-Gum...
فاكهة المطاط
Big Sis!
!أختاه
Elephant Gun!
إيليفنت
– Master Page One! – Are you okay?!
هل أنت بخير يا بيج ون-ساما؟
Master Page One...
...أن يُطاح ببيج ون-ساما هكذا
You damn rat bastard...!
أيها الحقير
How dare you do that to Pay-Pay?!
كيف تجرؤ على فعل ذلك بباي-تان؟
I'll destroy you!
!لأحطمنَّك
Master Ulti turned into a dinosaur, too!
تحولت أولتي-ساما إلى ديناصور هي الأخرى
Please! The castle can't take much more!
هذا محال، لن تتحمل القلعة أكثر من ذلك
She's... so strong!
إنها لشديدةُ البأس حقًّا
Ulti-Meteor!
ميتيور
Oh no!
لا جدوى
Gear Fourth!
فورث
Thunder Bagua!
هاكي
Straw Hat Luffy!
...أنت قبعة القش لوفي
It's you, isn't it?!
أليس كذلك؟...
That's me.
هذا صحيح
I...
...أنا
Who are you?!
من أنت يا هذا؟
He's getting away!
إنه يهرب بعيدًا
Catch him!
أمسكوه
I'm sorry!
المعذرة، ليس في نيتي أذيتك
Yeah, you don't seem like you will...
...أجل، لم يظهر أنك تحاول أذيتي
Listen, I gotta go!
أنصت، عليّ الإسراع
I've been waiting for you!
كنتُ أترقب مجيئك
Finally! You're finally here!
وأخيرًا أتيتَ إلى هنا
Indeed, I've been waiting for you!
...كنتُ أترقب مجيئك
Waiting for so very long!
...لوقتٍ طويل
My name is Yamato!
...اسمي ياماتو
I'm Kaido's son!
!وأنا ابن كايدو...